<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Static Site Generators on Valerie's Blog</title><link>https://hugo-toha.github.io/tags/static-site-generators/</link><description>Recent content in Static Site Generators on Valerie's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 08:07:25 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hugo-toha.github.io/tags/static-site-generators/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Index Websites with Google Search Console</title><link>https://hugo-toha.github.io/posts/google-search-console/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 08:07:25 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://hugo-toha.github.io/posts/google-search-console/</guid><description>In this post I&amp;rsquo;d like to show you how to use the Google Search Console to index your website.
The Google Search Console offers tools and reports to help you measure your site&amp;rsquo;s search traffic and performance, fix issues, and improve Google Search results. For a website to show up in a search engines (e.g. Google, Bing, etc.), the website needs to be indexed by the search engine. This can take between a few days, weeks to even months if indexing is not explicitly requested using the Google Search Console.</description></item><item><title>Generate Markdown Content Using Power Automate</title><link>https://hugo-toha.github.io/posts/auto-generate-markdown-content/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 08:06:25 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://hugo-toha.github.io/posts/auto-generate-markdown-content/</guid><description>In this post I&amp;rsquo;d like to show you how to use Microsoft Power Automate to generate markdown content for your MkDocs project.
Power Automate is a cloud-based process automation service that can be used to create automated workflows to synchronize and collect data, get notifications, start approvals, and more.
About this Use Case There are multiple reasons to automate content creation. In our case, we wanted to make it easier for non-developers to publish news in the &amp;ldquo;Latest News&amp;rdquo; section of our HelpCenter, see screenshot below.</description></item><item><title>Migrating from Jekyll to MkDocs</title><link>https://hugo-toha.github.io/posts/jekyll-to-mkdocs-migration/</link><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 08:06:25 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://hugo-toha.github.io/posts/jekyll-to-mkdocs-migration/</guid><description>Our company (or rather I as the technical writer responsible for our documentation) recently decided to say goodbye to our current solution for creating documentation: Jekyll. Instead, we are now working on migrating our existing content to MkDocs.
In this post I want to tell you a little bit about the reasons behind this decision.
Status Quo Currently, we still use Jekyll 3 to build our documentation.
Jekyll is a static site generator that uses static Markdown files and converts them to a website.</description></item></channel></rss>