<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Valerie's Blog</title><link>https://hugo-toha.github.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Valerie's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 08:06:25 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hugo-toha.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduction</title><link>https://hugo-toha.github.io/posts/introduction/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2024 08:06:25 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://hugo-toha.github.io/posts/introduction/</guid><description>Hi and welcome to my blog, where I post random stuff that I deal with during my work as a technical editor in a software company.
My Role As mentioned above, I work as a technical editor at a software company. When I started this job in 2021, I was a career changer (former application engineer). While I had some experience writing software documentation, I wasn&amp;rsquo;t trained in the field of writing / documenting.</description></item><item><title>Generate Markdown Content Using Power Automate</title><link>https://hugo-toha.github.io/posts/auto-generate-markdown-content/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2022 08:06:25 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://hugo-toha.github.io/posts/auto-generate-markdown-content/</guid><description>In this post I&amp;rsquo;d like to show you how to use Microsoft Power Automate to generate markdown content for your MkDocs project.
Power Automate is a cloud-based process automation service that can be used to create automated workflows to synchronize and collect data, get notifications, start approvals, and more.
About this Use Case There are multiple reasons to automate content creation. In our case, we wanted to make it easier for non-developers to publish news in the &amp;ldquo;Latest News&amp;rdquo; section of our HelpCenter, see screenshot below.</description></item><item><title>Migrating from Jekyll to MkDocs</title><link>https://hugo-toha.github.io/posts/jekyll-to-mkdocs-migration/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 08:06:25 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://hugo-toha.github.io/posts/jekyll-to-mkdocs-migration/</guid><description>Our company (or rather I as the technical writer responsible for our documentation) recently decided to say goodbye to our current solution for creating documentation: Jekyll. Instead, we are now working on moving our existing content to MkDocs.
In this post I want to tell you a little bit about the reasons behind this decision.
Status Quo Currently, we still use Jekyll 3 to build our documentation.
Jekyll is a static site generator that uses static Markdown files and converts them to a website.</description></item></channel></rss>